ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- OSH Occupational Safety and Health Forum, 1989-1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- OSH OECD (Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development), 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- OSH Personal Protective Equipment, 1977-1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- OSH Philadelphia Area Project on Occupational Safety and Health, 1976-1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- OSH Privacy, 1979-1995 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- OSH Progressive Alliance, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- OSH Radiation, 1975-1984 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- OSH Rayon, 1972-1980 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- OSH Rayon Industry, 1938-1972 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- OSH Reproductive Hazards, 1976-1996 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- OSH Reproductive Hazards, 1977-1989 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- OSH Reproductive Hazards Literature, 1980-1989 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- OSH Respiratory Diseases, 1974-1982 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- OSH Respiratory Diseases NIOSH Laboratory Management Seminar, 1976-1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- OSH Respiratory Diseases WHO Workshops, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- OSH Safety, 1972-1986 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- OSH Saint Augustine College, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- OSH Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- OSH Selikoff, Dr. Irving J., 1971-1992 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- OSH Selikoff, Dr. Irving J., 1970 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- OSH Shoe Industry, 1982-1993 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- OSH Reproductive Hazards, 1977-1989 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- OSH Reproductive Hazards Literature, 1980-1989 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- OSH Respiratory, 1974-1982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- OSH Respiratory Diseases NIOSH Laboratory Management Seminar, 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- OSH Respiratory Diseases WHO Workshops, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- OSH Safety, 1972-1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- OSH Saint Augustine College, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- OSH Selikoff, Dr. Irving J., 1971-1992 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- OSH Selikoff, Dr. Irving J., 1970 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- OSH Shoe Industry, 1982-1993 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- OSH Smoking, 1979-1987 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- OSH Society for Occupation and Environmental Health (II), 1975-1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- OSH Society for Occupational and Environmental Health (I), 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- OSH Society for Occupational and Environmental Health Finance Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- OSH South Africa AFL-CIO, 1984-1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- OSH South Africa Anglo-American Corporation, 1985-1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- OSH South Africa Bata. LTD., 1982-1985 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- OSH South Africa Canada, 1984-1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- OSH South Africa CLUW, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- OSH South Africa Congress of South African Trade Unions, 1985-1991 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- OSH South Africa Frame Corporation, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- OSH South Africa International Confederation pf Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1983-1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- OSH South Africa International Metal Workers' Federation, 1984-1987 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- OSH South Africa ITGLWF, 1983-1989 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- OSH South Africa Labor Committee Against Apartheid (LCAA), 1983-1987 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- OSH South Africa National Union of Mine Workers, 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- OSH South Africa SACTU (South African Congress of Trade Unions), 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- OSH South Africa Sullivan Code, 1983-1985 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- OSH South Africa United Nations, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- OSH Southern Institute for Occupational Health, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- OSH Southern Organizing Committee (SOC), 1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- OSH Soviet Union, 1982-1991 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  Russian
- OSH SRI International, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- OSH State Regulation, 1967-1971 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- OSH Statistics, 1970-1988 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- OSH Statistics NAS (National Academy of Sciences), 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- OSH Statistics NCVHS (National Committee on Vital and Health Statistics), 1977-1994 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- OSH Stress, 1980-1999 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- OSH Surveillance, 1986-1993 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- OSH Surveillance Injuries, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- OSH Surveillance State Laws, 1982-1993 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Surveillance State Laws - New Jersey, 1985-1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- OSH Surveillance State Laws - New York, 1981-1988 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- OSH Sweden, 1975-1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- OSH Synthetic Fibers, Inc., 1977-1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- OSH Textile Industry, 1978-1994 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- OSH TNCOSH, 1980-1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- OSH Toxicology, 1982-1994 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- OSH Union Activity (Other than AFL-CIO, IUD), 1972-1980 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- OSH Union Administration, 1971-1979 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- OSH United Kingdom, 1971-1991 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- OSH United Kingdom (II) Safety Representatives, 1979-1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- OSH Universities Empire State College, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- OSH Universities Mount Sinai, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- OSH Urban Environmental Conferences, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- OSH URW-Rubber Industry Studies, 1976-1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- OSH Video Display Terminals, 1979-1989 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- OSH WISH (Worker's Institute for Safety and Health), 1979-1986 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- OSH Women, 1972-1993 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- OSH Women's Occupational Health Resource Center, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- OSH Work Organization, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- OSH Wool Literature, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- OSH WYNCOSH (Western NY Council of Occupational Safety and Health), 1982-1988 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- OSH-Administration Appropriations, 1989-1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- OSH-Administration Ballenger Bill, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- OSH-Administration BLS (Bureau of Labor Statistics), 1982-1995 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- OSH Administration BLS Annual Survey, 1986-1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- OSH-Administration Keystone Project, 1987-1990 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- OSH Administration BLS LRAC, 1986-1995 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- OSH-Administration BLS LRAC (Labor Research Advisory Committee), 1986-1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- OSH-Administration BLS Redesign, 1988-1991 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- OSH-Administration BLS Region (III), 1990-1993 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- OSH-Administration BLS State Health Department, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- OSH-Administration BLS Symposium, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- OSH Administration BLS Work Injury Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- OSH-Administration Congressional Oversight, 1988-1996 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- OSH-Administration General, 1983-1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- OSH-Administration Reform, 1988-1994 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- OSH-Administration Reform AFL-CIO, 1989-1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- OSH-Administration Reform Clipping, 1991-1994 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- OSH-Administration Reform NYS State, 1988-1994 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- OSH-Administration Reform Democratic Position, 1970-1994 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- OSH-Administration Reform House Hearings, 1991-1993 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- OSH-Administration Reform Industry Position, 1991-1993 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- OSH-Administration Reform Lobbying, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- OSH-Administration Reform Senate Hearings, 1992-1995 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- OSH-Administration Regulatory Reform, 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- OSH-Administration Review Commission, 1983-1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- OSH-Administration State Plans, 1983-2001 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- OSH-Administration State Plans NC, 1983-1996 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- OSH-Administration State Plans SC, 1983-1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Clean Air Act, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Enforcement Region 4, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Enforcement Sampling (VI-A), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department General, 1983-1994 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping (II-A) Access Standard, 1980-1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- OSH Administration Labor Department Record Keeping (II-B) Congressional Oversight, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping (II-B) Congressional Oversight, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping (II-C) Enforcement, 1986-1996 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Recordkeeping, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping, 1970-1994 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Record Keeping Discussions, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Standards (III), 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Standards (III) OTA Panel, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- OSH-Administration Labor Departments Standards(III) PEL Revisions, 1988-1993 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Standards (III) Programs, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- OSH-Administration Labor Department Standards (III-A) Respirators, 1983-1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- OSH Administration Labor Department Standards-Method of Compliance Requirement ACTWU Testimony, 1983-1993 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH ERC (Educational Resource Center), 1986-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH General, 1981-2001 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH High Risk Workers, 1967-1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH Medical Surveillance, 1986-1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH Surveillance, 1983-1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH Surveillance, 1987-1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- OSH-Surveillance Congressional Oversight, 1983-1991 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- OSH-Administration NIOSH Surveillance Literature, 1986-1999 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- A & A Midwest Rebuilders, Chicago IL (Box 62, Folder 1)
- OSH Case A and A Midwest Rebuilders Chicago, Illinois, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Accurate Lace Dye Co., NY (Box 62, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Accurate Lace Dye Company, New York, New York, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Abe Sohn Dyers, NY (Box 62, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Abe Sohn Dyers New York, New York, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Acme Engraving Co., Passaic NJ (Box 62, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Acme Engraving Company, Passaic, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Accu Screen, W. Babylon NY (Box 62, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Acme Engraving Company, Passaic, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Adam Sponging Corp., Boston MA (Box 62, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Accu Screen West Babylon, New York, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Adelaide Mills (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Adams Sponging Corporation Boston, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Advo System Inc., Pittsburgh PA (Box 62, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Adelaide Mills, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Airguard Ind., Louisville, KY (Box 62, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Advo System, Inc. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Allen Ind., Inc. (subs. of Dayco Corp.) Herrin IL 72-76 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Allen Industries, Inc. (subs. Of Dayco Corporation) Herrin, Illinois, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Allen Morrison Inc., Lynchburg, VA (Box 62, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Allen Morrison, Inc. Lynchburg, Virginia, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Allesons of Rochester, Inc. Geneva NY (Box 62, Folder 12)
- OSHA Case Allied Chemical Company Knoxville, Tennessee, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Allied Chemical Corp., Knoxville, TN (Box 62, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Alton Box Board Company Cedartown, Georgia, 1981-1984 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Alton Box Board, Co., Cedartown, GA (Box 62, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Alton Packaging Corporation Mount Home, North Carolina, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Alton Packaging, Mt. Home, NC (Box 62, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Amerbelle Corporation Rockville, Connecticut, 1983-1986 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Amerbelle Corp., Rockville, CT (Box 62, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Amerbelle Corporation Vernon, Connecticut, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Amerbelle Corp., Vernon, CT (Box 62, Folder 17)
- OSH Case American Art Textile Packaging Company, Inc. New York, NY, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- American Art Textile Ptg. Co.,lnc. NYC (Box 62, Folder 18)
- OSHA Case American Can Company, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- American Can Company, Greenwich CT (Box 62, Folder 19)
- OSH Case American Greeting Card Company Greenville, Tennessee, 1980-1982 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- American Greeting Card Co., Greenville, TN (Box 62, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Anchor Hocking Corp. Cranston, NJ, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Anchor Hocking Corp., Cranston NJ (Box 62, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Androme Leather Company, Inc. Gloversville, NY, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Androme Leather Co., Inc. Gloversville, NY (Box 62, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Angelica Healthcare Services Inc. Milford, Connecticut, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Angelica Healthcare Services, Inc. Milford, CT (Box 62, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Ann Albrizio, Inc. New York, NY, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Ann Albrizio Inc., NYC (Box 62, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Applikay Textile Process Corporation, Passaic, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Applikay Textile Process Corp., Passaic, NJ (Box 62, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Apollo Dyeing and Finishing Paterson, New Jersey, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Apollo Dyeing and Finishing, Paterson, NJ (Box 62, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Ari Plastics Panama City, Florida, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Ari Plastics, Panama City, FL (Box 62, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Arista Novelty Print Company, Yonkers, New York, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Arista Novelty Print Co., Yonkers, NY (Box 62, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Armitage Shanks, Inc. Mooresville, North Carolina, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Armitage Shanks, Inc. Mooresville, NC (Box 62, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Armstrong World Ind. Fulton, New York, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Armstrong World Ind., Fulton NY (Box 62, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Arrow Shirt Company Austell Warehouse Atlanta, Georgia, 1983-1988 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Arrow Shirt Co., Austell Warehouse, Atlanta GA (Box 62, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Ashworth Brothers, Inc. Fall River, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Ashworth Bros., Inc. Fall Rivers, MA (Box 62, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Atlantic Textile Packaging Incorporated Company, New York, New York, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Atlantic Tex., Ptg. Inc., Co., NYC (Box 62, Folder 33)
- OSH Case ATP Processors Ltd. Paterson, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- ATP Processors ltd. Paterson, NJ (Box 62, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Avalon Dyeing and Finishing Company, Inc. Haledon, New Jersey, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Avalon Dyeing and Finishing Co., Inc. Haledon, NJ (Box 62, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Avon Knitting Mills, Inc. Fairview, New Jersey, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Avon Knitting Mills, Fairview, NJ (Box 62, Folder 36)
- OSHA Case Avtex Fibers, Inc. General, 1977-1989 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Avtex Fibers Inc., General (Box 62, Folder 37)
- OSHA Case Avtex Fibers, Inc. Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1978-1985 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Avtex Fibers Inc., Meadville, PA (Box 62, Folder 38)
- OSH Case Avtex Fibers Lewistown, Pennsylvania, 1979-1986 (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Avtex Fibers Inc., Lewistown, PA (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Avtex Fibers Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Avtex Fibers Inc., Front Royal, VA (Box 62, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Babbitt Bearings, Inc. Syracuse, New York, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Babbitt Bearings, Inc. Syracuse, NY (Box 62, Folder 41)
- OSH Case Bachrack Inc. Watertown, Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Bachrack Inc., Watertown, MA (Box 62, Folder 42)
- OSHA Ballet Fabric Company, Scottsboro, Alabama, 1977-1982 (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Ballet Fabric Co., Scottsboro, AI (Box 62, Folder 43)
- OSH Case Baltic Dyeing and Finishing, Passaic, New Jersey, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Baltic Dyeing and Finishing, Passaic, NJ (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Bama Mills Div. Fabric - Amer. Corp. (Box 63, Folder 1)
- OSHA Case Bama Mill Division, Fabrics America Corporation (subsidiary of Allied Product Corporation), 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Bass J. & Co., Hazeltown, PA (Box 63, Folder 2)
- OSHA Case J. Bass and Company, Inc. Hazelton, Pennsylvania, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Bates Fabric Inc., Lewistown, ME (Box 63, Folder 3)
- OSHA Case Bates Fabrics, Inc. Lewiston, Maine, 1977-1980 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Batesville Casket Co., Inc. Nashua, NH (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Batesville Casket Company, Inc. Nashua, New Hampshire, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Beattie Mfg., Co., Inc. Littlefalls, NJ (Box 63, Folder 5)
- OSHA Case Beattie Manufacturing Company, Inc. Little Falls, New Jersey, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Bee Chemical, Fairfield, NJ (Box 63, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Bee Chemical Company Fairfield, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Belding Hemingway (S. Hampton Text) Emporia, VA (Box 63, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Belding Hemingway (Southampton Textiles) Emporia, Virginia, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Belton Corp., Belton, SC (Box 63, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Belton Corporation Belton, South Carolina, 1979-1983 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Bemis Company. Flemington, NJ (Box 63, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case Bemis Company, Inc. Buffalo, New York (Box 63, Folder 9)
  No Contents in Folder
- Bemis Company. Bemis, TN (Box 63, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Bemis Company, Inc. Flemington, New Jersey, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Bemis Company. Indianapolis, IN (Box 63, Folder 11)
- OSHA Case Bemis Company Collective Bargaining, Bemis, Tennessee, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Bemis Company. Louisiana, MO (Box 63, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Bemis Company, Houston, Texas, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Bemis Company. Omaha, Nebraska (Box 63, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Bemis Company, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Bemis Company. Terre Haute, IN (Box 63, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Bemis Company, Louisiana, MO, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Berkshire Hathaway, Inc. New Bedford, MA (Box 63, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Bemis Company, Omaha, Nebraska, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Bernel Foam Products Corp., Buffalo, NY (Box 63, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case Bemis Company, Inc. Terre Haute, Ind., 1986 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Bernzomatic (Div. of Newell Cos., Inc.) Medina, NY (Box 63, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Berkshire Hathaway Inc. New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Bernen Rug Mills, Fresno, CA (Box 63, Folder 18)
- OSHA Case Bernel Foam Products Corporation, Buffalo, New York, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Birdair Structure Inc., Cheetowaga, NY (Box 63, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Bernzomatic Div. Newell Cos. Inc. Medina, New York, 1982-1988 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Birdseye Inc., Gen. Food Corp. Fulton, NY (Box 63, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Berven Rug Mills, Fresno, California, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Bixby International Corp., Newburyport, MA (Box 63, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Birdair Structures Inc. Cheektowaga, New York, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Bluebird Silk Mfg., Co. (Box 63, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Birdseye, Inc. General Foods Corporation, Fulton, New York, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Blueridge Winkler Co., Bangor, PA (Box 63, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Bittick Associates Inc. D/B/A Poco Tech Industries, East Stroudsberg, Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Blueridge Winkler Co., (subs. Lehigh Valley Ind.) Bangor, PA (Box 63, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Bixby International Corporation, Newburyport, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Boise Cascade Corp., Rochester, NY (Box 63, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Blue Bird Silk Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Botany 500, Inc., Phil. PA (Box 63, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Blue Ridge Winkler Company, Bangor, Pennsylvania, 1981-1983 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Brand-Rex Co., Wilimantic, CT (Box 63, Folder 27)
- OSHA Case Blue Ridge-Winkler, Inc (subs. Lehigh Valley Industries.) Bangor, Pennsylvania, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Brawer Brothers Inc., Empire Dyeing Div., Haledon, NJ (Box 63, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Boise Cascade Corporation, Rochester, New York, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Brewnermans - Oswego, NY (Box 63, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Botany 500, Inc. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Brewster Finishing Co., Inc. Paterson, NJ (Box 63, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Brand-Rex Company, Willimantic, Connecticut, 1981-1987 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Bridgeton Dyeing and Finishing (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Brawer Brothers, Inc. Empire Dyeing Division, Haledon, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Bridgeton, NJ Bridgewater Mfg., Co. South Bound Brook, NJ (Box 63, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Brewnerman's, Oswego, New York, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Brook William Shoes co., Nelsonville, OH (Box 63, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Brewster Finishing Company, Inc. Paterson, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- BRW, Sylvester, GA (Box 63, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Bridgeton Dyeing and Finishing, Bridgeton, New Jersey, 1976-1983 (Box 63, Folder 34)
- BRW Ind. Inc., Bangor PA (Box 63, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Bridgewater Manufacturing Company, South Bound Brook, New Jersey, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Buffalo Batt and Felt Corp., Depew, NY (Box 63, Folder 36)
- Brigadier Industries, Sylvester, Georgia, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 36)
- Burlington Ind. General (Box 63, Folder 37)
- OSH Case William Brook Shoe Company, Nelsonville, Ohio, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 37)
- Burlington Ind. Hillsville, GA (Box 63, Folder 38)
- OSH Case BRW Sylvester, Georgia, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 38)
- Burlington Ind. (see Erwin Mills Div.) Erwin, NC (Box 63, Folder 39)
- OSH Case Burlington Ind. Inc. Hillsville, Virginia, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 39)
- Burlington Ind. Kernersville, NC (Box 63, Folder 40)
- OSH Case BRW Industries, Inc. Bangor, Pennsylvania, 1983-1985 (Box 63, Folder 40)
- Burlington Ind. Stonewall, Miss. (Box 63, Folder 41)
- OSH Case Burlington Industries see Erwin Mills Div. Erwin, North Carolina, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 41)
- Buster Brown Apparel, Chattanooga, TN (Box 63, Folder 42)
- Burlington Ind. Kernersville, North Carolina, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 42)
- Byron & Sons, Inc., W.D. (subs. Walter Kiddie and Co., Williamsport, MD (Box 63, Folder 43)
- OSHA Case Burlington Industries, Stonewall, Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 43)
- Calidonian Dye Works, Phil. PA (Box 63, Folder 44)
- OSH Case Buster Brown Apparel Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1986-1990 (Box 63, Folder 44)
- Cannon Mills. General (Box 63, Folder 45)
- OSH Case W.D. Byron and Sons, Inc. (subs. Walter Kiddie and Company) Williamsport, Maryland, 1978-1987 (Box 63, Folder 45)
- Cannon Mills. Kannapolis, NC (Box 63, Folder 46)
- OSH Case Calidonian Dye Works, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 46)
- OSH Case Cannon Mills Company General, 1984-1985 (Box 63, Folder 47)
- Barney Knight vs Cannon Mills Assorted Documents (Box 63, Folder 48)
- OSHA Case Cannon Mills Kannapolis, North Carolina, 1980-1985 (Box 63, Folder 49)
- Cannon Mills. Salisbury, NC (Box 64, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Cannon Mills Company, Salisbury, North Carolina, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Canton Textile Mills, Inc., Canton, GA 1978 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Canton Textile Mills, Inc. Canton Georgia, 1978-1981 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Canton Mfg. Co., Canton, IL (Box 64, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Canton Manufacturing Company, Canton, Illinois, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Can-Tex Ind., Cannelton, Ind. (Box 64, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Canton Textile Mills, Inc. Canton, Georgia, 1976-1981 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- CAPCO, Grand Junction, CO (Box 64, Folder 5)
- OSHA Case Can-Tex Ind. Cannelton, Inc., 1978 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- CAP - Weatherization, Duluth, MO (Box 64, Folder 6)
- OSH Case CAPCO Grand Junction, Colorado, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Cape Cod Sportswear Co., Inc., New Bedford, MA (Box 64, Folder 7)
- CAP Weatherization, Duluth, MN Twin Cities Joint Board., 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Capitol Dye Works, Inc., NY, NY (Box 64, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Cape Cod Sports-Wear Company, Inc. New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 8)